<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Venting on Adam.Blog()</title>
    <link>http://adampresley.com/tags/venting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Venting on Adam.Blog()</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 18:27:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://adampresley.com/tags/venting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>NTTA to raise speed limits - Woo Hoo!</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/ntta-to-raise-speed-limits-woo-hoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 18:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/ntta-to-raise-speed-limits-woo-hoo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I learned that the North Texas Toll Authority, affectionately
known as NTTA, has requested that the speed limits be raised by 10 miles
per hour on our major toll road areas, including the North Dallas
Tollway and the President George Bush Tollway. It appears that the NTTA
has not raised the speed limits, which currently stand between 55 and 60
MPH, because of a failure to conduct the state&amp;rsquo;s required speed safety
tests, prohibiting the much desired raise in limit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I for one am quite happy to hear this news. It pains me to know that I
could get a ticket for going over &lt;strong&gt;55 freakin miles per hour&lt;/strong&gt; on a
road that &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;I HAVE TO PAY TO DRIVE ON!!!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Good grief, and about time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day One of Redemption</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/day-one-of-redemption/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2007 05:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/day-one-of-redemption/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yes, today is the first day of redemption for Chic-Fil-A. Yes, that&amp;rsquo;s
right. They got my order correct! YAY!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chic-Fil-A Strikes Again!</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/chic-fil-a-strikes-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/chic-fil-a-strikes-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GAH!! Tis so frustrating when you wish to have a bit of breakfast on the
way to work, and the drive-thru fails you by messing up your order. Once
again, Chick-Fil-A has made my morning less bright. This time they left
out my hashbrowns. Alas. :(&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Without the Chicken!</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/without-the-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2007 02:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/without-the-chicken/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I just HAD to put it out there, this little ditty about a chicken
biscuit gone horribly wrong. One of the daily routines that Maryanne and
I have in our morning commute to work is to stop off at either
McDonald&amp;rsquo;s or Chik-fil-A to get a bite to eat for breakfast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ordered my usual on this Thursday morning in the Chic-Fil-A
drive-thru: A number 1, add egg and cheese, with a large unsweet tea. We
picked up the order at the window and began to drive away, me pulling
out the contents of this bag o&amp;rsquo; goodies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hand Maryanne her breakfast burrito and then proceed to extract my
biscuit. To my great alarm and dismay, however, I discovered that my
chicken biscuit with egg and cheese was missing one critical element&amp;hellip;
The chicken! RUINED!!! The day was RUINED!!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>