<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nerdy on Adam.Blog()</title>
    <link>http://adampresley.com/tags/nerdy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nerdy on Adam.Blog()</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2010 21:59:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://adampresley.com/tags/nerdy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>2010 Date Nerdiness</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/2010-date-nerdiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2010 21:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/2010-date-nerdiness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So my girlfriend and I were discussing some plans we&amp;rsquo;ve gotta make this
year, and started talking about cool dates. You know, like 9/9/1999. The
coolest one so far for this year would be 10/10/2010 (ten ten ten).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So anyone who has ever known me knows that not only am I a giant nerd,
but I own it. I immediately recognized that 10/10/10 could be
represented in binary as 101010. And then I busted out a calculator
because I suck at converting binary to decimal. And guess what???&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;101010 = 42!!!!&lt;/strong&gt; The answer to the ultimate question of life, the
universe, and everything!! How super cool is that?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Find Yahoo Widgets Offscreen</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/how-to-find-yahoo-widgets-offscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/how-to-find-yahoo-widgets-offscreen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For those that enjoy the features offered by the &lt;a href=&#34;http://widgets.yahoo.com&#34;&gt;Yahoo! Widgets&lt;/a&gt; you
might at some point find yourself in a situation similar to what I
experienced today. Somehow, perhaps with my two monitor goodness, and
goofing that up by logging into our VPN, I tried to open up the
&lt;a href=&#34;http://widgets.yahoo.com/widgets/widget-converter&#34;&gt;Converter widget&lt;/a&gt;, and it never showed up on the screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a bit of digging I at least found out how to reset the widget&amp;rsquo;s
position, even though I didn&amp;rsquo;t find out why it disappeared. If you find
that launching a widget gives you a non-visible widget, you may wish to
try the following.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open Regedit (Start -&amp;gt; Run -&amp;gt; Regedit)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Browse to HKEY_CURRENT_USER\Software\Yahoo\WidgetEngine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Find the folder with the name of the widget. Under this folder will likely be a folder named Windows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under the Windows folder there should be a main folder. Open this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delete the key named Positions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Restart the widget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good widgeting!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reasons for Excitement</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/reasons-for-excitement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2007 05:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/reasons-for-excitement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two reasons for my excitement this morning, and I shall sum them up
promptly: Lord of the Rings Online content update, and Street Fighter
IV. That&amp;rsquo;s right, you heard it. Street Fighter IV! I LOVED the old
Street Fighter games. I grew up playing those in the arcades all day
long, and then on my Super Nintendo. Pimp times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And to make it even better this month Turbine will be releasing their
next major content update, Bood 11, for Lord of the Rings Online. This
update features grand coolness like player and kinship housing, complete
with furnishings and vendor discounts, and even taxidermy. Also on the
docket are new quests, and a brand new 12 player raid instance in which
you face off with a Balroq! Rock on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out both of these at these links:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gamesradar.com/us/ps3/game/news/article.&#34;&gt;Street Fighter IV&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lotro.turbine.com/article/421&#34;&gt;Book 11 - Lord of the Rings Online&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anewen Reaches 40!</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/anewen-reaches-40/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2007 17:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/anewen-reaches-40/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yay! My main character in Lord of the Rings Online: Shadows of Angmar
just reached level 40! Woo hoo! Soon I shall be a level 50 champion
renown throughout Middle Earth! :p&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guitar 2, denied!</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/guitar-2-denied/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2006 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/guitar-2-denied/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I went to Fry&amp;rsquo;s Electronics tonight in search of a second guitar for my
Guitar Hero 2 game. This is prompted by the fact that I was under the
impression that my current second guitar was broken. Notice I said
&amp;ldquo;impression&amp;rdquo;. Turns out a lot of the third party guitars simply do not
work with Guitar Hero 2! And Fry&amp;rsquo;s has them up &lt;strong&gt;EVERYWHERE&lt;/strong&gt; while
promoting Guitar Hero 2. How do I know they don&amp;rsquo;t work? I actually took
the guitar out of the box, plugged it in to their display, and tested
it. Same behavior as mine, the green button doesn&amp;rsquo;t work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And go figure, they don&amp;rsquo;t sell &lt;strong&gt;JUST&lt;/strong&gt; the first party guitar. &amp;lt;_&amp;lt;
BAH!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>