<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mobile on Adam.Blog()</title>
    <link>http://adampresley.com/tags/mobile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mobile on Adam.Blog()</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2007 08:18:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://adampresley.com/tags/mobile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Development</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/mobile-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2007 08:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/mobile-development/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Several months ago I purchased a new cell phone because I decided to
join the cool people and jump on the media/internet/do it all phone
bandwagon. With this in mind I purchased the Helio Ocean. Almost
$300 cheaper than the iPhone this puppy has most of the best features
found on a cell phone to date, with a service plan that is fairly
priced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course the developer in me saw that this phone uses Java technology
for its applications. Hey, I know Java! I should write an application.
The problem was that I had no real application need at the time so I
shrugged it off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until now. Just two weeks ago I joined the Weight Watchers program
in an attempt to lose weight. In case you aren&amp;rsquo;t aware, Weight Watchers
uses a point system which is based off calorie, fat, and fiber content.
Perfect! I need a little application on my phone to enter in calories,
fat, and fiber and it spit out the points count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turns out that the mobile development part wasn&amp;rsquo;t so difficult. The hard
part is getting your Java application &lt;strong&gt;TO&lt;/strong&gt; your Helio and getting it to
&lt;strong&gt;EXECUTE&lt;/strong&gt;. The folks at Helio apparently do not wish third party
people developing applications without their blessing so they require
you to purchase a developer license from them. No thanks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A little looking around on the internet turns up a few peeps who have
figured out that Helio simply renames their JAR files, and adds two
signatures to it. This coupled with a descriptor file allows you to
download your custom application to your Helio device and execute it. So
as a result I have made my first draft of the Weight Watchers points
calculator application. It is VERY rough right now, and needs a bit of
work. It is also not 100% accurate in the calculation, but it is pretty
close, so it will work as a means to calculate points in a hurry or on
the go. Meanwhile I will continue spicing the app up and once done will
post on my website for consumption by not only Helio users, but also
anyone who has a Java enabled phone.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>