<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General on Adam.Blog()</title>
    <link>http://adampresley.com/tags/general/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General on Adam.Blog()</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://adampresley.com/tags/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Communication Is An Interesting Thing</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/communication-is-an-interesting-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/communication-is-an-interesting-thing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There has been a lot of talk about effective communication in my day-to-day lately. At work I have set goals to work on improving how I communicate with coworkers and superiors. On-line I see talk in communities about how to effectively conduct discussions and dialog. In all of this it seems that being able to talk about something, convince someone, or even disseminate information can be an interesting and challenging thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What makes this so dang hard??&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;!-- excerpt --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is it that you want to accomplish when you open a dialog with someone? Why do you reply to a post on a forum? When you send an email reply to someone asking for your professional opinion what do you hope to achieve? Simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You want to be heard. You hope you have something useful to contribute to the
conversation. You may even want to convince someone to see things from your
perspective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what happens when we engage in a dialog or try to convince someone of some thing? The other party has to listen. This is where things get tricky. When you begin listening to someone else&amp;rsquo;s opinion, or read that email reply or forum response, you are going to frame what is said based on a few factors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Context of the conversation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your own experiences related to the subject&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trigger words/phrases will come into play&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When engaging in dialog of any form what you say or write will be heard and read by someone who will apply their own experiences within what they perceive the context to be. Couple this with the chance of triggers and one must be careful. For example let&amp;rsquo;s say that someone is asking for help on a subject and they post this in a forum. I open this forum thread and start to read. Immediately I start to build up a context for this dialog. This context will be affected by previous experiences or trigger words and phrases. Let&amp;rsquo;s say that the forum post looks something like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Help! I cannot find the answer to my question, and it just doesn&#39;t work! What do I do?&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps in the past I have had bad experiences with helping people who never bother to help themselves. Maybe these people never read the manual, even though there may have been &lt;em&gt;great&lt;/em&gt; resources available for them to help themselves! Immediately I might start to frame this new dialog with that context, and start to apply my previous bad experiences to this conversation. My response might look like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Ya know, a quick Stack Overflow search found it in 30 seconds.&lt;/code&gt;
&lt;code&gt;There is documentation, RTFM!&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is wrong with my response? Technically it is accurate. A quick search may indeed find that there is awesome documentation to this question. Perhaps the poster should have indeed checked around for said documentation. So why is this response not the best strategy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My response is retaliatory. I am aggressive due to previous experiences.
The poster used trigger phrases that made me think of negative experiences.
My response, in turn, will be a bad experience for the poster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not tailoring my response for my audience in a way that will best
reach them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He is the problem. My audience, the poster, may not get the real intent of the message because I did not consider the best way to communicate what I want them to hear. They may not even get the intent of my message because at this point I am not speaking in a way that would cause them to positively listen and grok what I&amp;rsquo;m saying. How could I have said this differently? How about something like this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Hi. I&#39;m sorry to hear you are having trouble. What techniques have&lt;/code&gt;
&lt;code&gt;you tried so far? I notice that there are some great examples in the&lt;/code&gt;
&lt;code&gt;documentation that might address your specific problem.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This response does a couple of things. It first empathizes with the poster. Their post seems to indicate that they may have searched a bit, but they are frustrated. Secondly by asking what they have tried so far I am trying to politely ask the poster to talk more to what they have done. And if they haven&amp;rsquo;t tried anything themselves this is a gentle nudge to do so. Finally I point out that the documentation has things in it that might help their problem, which reminds them of the super-awesome-cool documentation that somebody took a lot of pain to write.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time my favorite response to emails that asked what I thought to be stupid questions was &lt;code&gt;No&lt;/code&gt;. I&amp;rsquo;ve started learning over the last few years that this approach alienated more often than it helped, causing people to not really hear the intent of my message. It also turned me on to the possibility that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t really hearing what they had to say as well, and that I might be missing something! Perhaps the next time you feel like laying down the hammer in an email, forum post, or even face-to-face conversation, stop and think about your audience. What is going to be most effective in communicating? I know I am continually trying to improve this myself.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Weapon Formed Debut Album Coming Soon!</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/no-weapon-formed-debut-album-coming-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/no-weapon-formed-debut-album-coming-soon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My brother and his band &lt;strong&gt;No Weapon Formed&lt;/strong&gt; will be releasing their debut album soon. The title of the album undetermined still but you can find a preview track YouTube named &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V_iXcK6vKrA&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be&#34;&gt;Phoenix&lt;/a&gt;. Go check it out and give it a like. These guys certainly have a great rock sound!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://adampresley.com/assets/adampresley/images/posts/no-weapon-formed-eye-1.png&#34; alt=&#34;No Weapon Formed&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CCISD Career Day 2014</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/ccisd-career-day-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/ccisd-career-day-2014/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last night the I participated as a representative for computer programming at the Clear Creek ISD College and Career Fair night. The Clear Creek school district offers a number of programs that encourage students to jump start their future education and careers. The job fair is a way for students to talk to actual practitioners in their field of interest, or even learn about opportunities they may have never known about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last night was quite a success in my book. There were almost 100 tables representing business &amp;amp; marketing, agriculture, science and technology, education, transportation, and health services. Many tables had flashy backdrops, table covers, literature and demonstrations. I didn&amp;rsquo;t quite have the flash, but I did have a small presentation running on a loop on my giant gaming laptop, which can be found &lt;a href=&#34;http://careerday2014.adampresley.com/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was originally concerned I would not have many visitors. Programming isn&amp;rsquo;t considered to be &lt;em&gt;exciting&lt;/em&gt; by a lot of people I know. That concern was unfounded. I had a busy night! Lots of kids came by asking a wide array of questions, from &amp;ldquo;how much money will I make&amp;rdquo; to the student who is already teaching themselves or in Computer Science Pre-AP classes. I was very impressed with some students and their drive to learn on their own, asking great questions for advice on ways to learn even more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had a great time, and look forward to doing another if the opportunity arises. And maybe next time I&amp;rsquo;ll make some flashy booth backdrops!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://adampresley.com/assets/adampresley/images/posts/adam-career-day-2014.png&#34; alt=&#34;Adam at Career Day&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resizing Multiple Images Using ImageMagick in Ubuntu</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/resizing-multiple-images-imagemagick-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2013 11:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/resizing-multiple-images-imagemagick-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever needed to resize a bunch of images in bulk? Most of us who do web development,
image manipulation, or blogging probably have at some point. If you are running in Ubuntu here
is a quick way to do this on the console.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34; style=&#34;background: #272822&#34;&gt;&lt;pre style=&#34;line-height: 125%&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;$ convert &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;*.JPG[800x&amp;gt;]&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt; new-name-%03d.jpg
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The above script will take all files with a &lt;strong&gt;.JPG&lt;/strong&gt; extension and resize them to 800 pixels
wide and name the new version of the file as &lt;em&gt;new-name-001.jpg&lt;/em&gt;. The &lt;strong&gt;%03d&lt;/strong&gt; tells
ImageMagick to add numbers sequentially using 3 digits. Pretty cool eh?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Community Professional Pins Are In!</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/adobe-community-professional-pins-are-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/adobe-community-professional-pins-are-in/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sweeeet. I got home and on my keyboard is sitting a letter from Liz
Frederick at Adobe. I open it up and discover that my nifty magnetic ACP
pin is in there, as well as stickers! I love stickers!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rings Are Purchased</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/rings-are-purchased/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2010 06:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/rings-are-purchased/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today Maryanne and I went for another round of wedding ring shopping. I
am pleased to announce that we have made our final decision and rings
have been purchased for both her and myself. We ended up making our
purchase at Zales from the manager Chris. It was actually a really great
experience working with him to pick out our rings. So many of the
previous sales people were&amp;hellip; well&amp;hellip; too &amp;ldquo;salesy&amp;rdquo;. I know that they are
&lt;strong&gt;supposed&lt;/strong&gt; to make the sale, but I honestly don&amp;rsquo;t need to
continually hear about &amp;ldquo;great value&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;superior service&amp;rdquo; and
&amp;ldquo;fantastic warranty&amp;rdquo;. Most &lt;strong&gt;all&lt;/strong&gt; jewelry providers offer some type
of warranty, and most all are interested in providing a good service, as
most all of them want my money!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chris at Zales was friendly, easy to talk to, and was quick to point out
the sales, specials, and not try to shove the $24,000 rings on
Maryanne&amp;rsquo;s fingers. If you would like to see a picture of her ring and
Maryanne&amp;rsquo;s account of the shopping experience you can visit our wedding
site,
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.adamandmaryannewedding.com&#34;&gt;http://www.adamandmaryannewedding.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, and yay! Another wedding checklist item marked off the list! Woo
hoo!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dallas TechFest 2010</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/dallas-techfest-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 01:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/dallas-techfest-2010/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I had the pleasure of attending and speaking at Dallas
TechFest 2010. I presented on taking an existing ColdFusion application
and spicing it up incrementally using &lt;a href=&#34;http://jquery.com&#34;&gt;jQuery&lt;/a&gt;, the hottest JavaScript
library around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The micro-conference; I suppose you can call it that, was a lot of fun.
I attended some pretty good sessions, including MySQL optimization,
Event Gateway programming in ColdFusion, and an introduction to Grails
and CouchDB. I must say that CouchDB is &lt;em&gt;particularly&lt;/em&gt; interesting,
and may find its way into one of my projects in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grouping Structures in Groovy</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/grouping-structures-in-groovy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 02:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/grouping-structures-in-groovy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A useful tidbit for those interested in playing around with Groovy. I
had need recently to take a structure, or more Groovy-like, a Map, and
group by a particular key, and iterate over the grouped items. Turns out
to be quite easy in Groovy. Let&amp;rsquo;s see an example of such a structure and
how one would &lt;em&gt;normally&lt;/em&gt; iterate over it and display the data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34; style=&#34;background: #272822&#34;&gt;&lt;pre style=&#34;line-height: 125%&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #66d9ef&#34;&gt;public&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #66d9ef&#34;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #a6e22e&#34;&gt;Example1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;()&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: #66d9ef&#34;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;sampleData&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;Adam Presley&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;Architect&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;id&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #ae81ff&#34;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;],&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;Collin Judd&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;Dev II&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;id&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #ae81ff&#34;&gt;15&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;],&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;Steve Goodly&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;Architect&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;id:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #ae81ff&#34;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;],&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;Chris Jordey&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;title:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;Dev&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;II&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;, id: 3 ],&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;Ben Nadel&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;title:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;ACP&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;, id: 5 ]&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;];&lt;/span&gt;

    &lt;span style=&#34;color: #75715e&#34;&gt;/*&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style=&#34;color: #75715e&#34;&gt;    * Display existing map.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style=&#34;color: #75715e&#34;&gt;    */&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;println&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;Existing structure:&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;sampleData&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #a6e22e&#34;&gt;each&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;println&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;Name: ${it.name}, title: &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;$&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #a6e22e&#34;&gt;title&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;;&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;println&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;As you can see iteration over the structure is fairly easy. Now I want
to actually group the structure items by the person&amp;rsquo;s title, iterate and
display the title, then each person who has that title. Here&amp;rsquo;s how,
using the same structure as above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34; style=&#34;background: #272822&#34;&gt;&lt;pre style=&#34;line-height: 125%&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #75715e&#34;&gt;/*&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style=&#34;color: #75715e&#34;&gt; * Group the data by title&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style=&#34;color: #75715e&#34;&gt; */&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;sampleData&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #a6e22e&#34;&gt;groupBy&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #a6e22e&#34;&gt;title&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;}.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #a6e22e&#34;&gt;each&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;group&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;-&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;println&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;*GROUP ${group.key}*&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;

    &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;group&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #a6e22e&#34;&gt;value&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #a6e22e&#34;&gt;each&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;item&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;-&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;println&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;Name: ${item.name}, title: &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;$&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;item&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #a6e22e&#34;&gt;title&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;;&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;

    &lt;span style=&#34;color: #f8f8f2&#34;&gt;println&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color: #e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style=&#34;color: #f92672&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you use the &lt;strong&gt;groupBy&lt;/strong&gt; method you return, through a closure, the
criteria to group by. Groovy then gives you a new structure, each key
being the value to group by, which is an array of the group matches.
Pretty cool!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope you enjoyed, and happy coding!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running on a VPS Now</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/running-on-a-vps-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/running-on-a-vps-now/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;About a week ago I moved all the code for my site onto a new VPS
(Virtual Private Server) provided by &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.2host.com&#34;&gt;2Host.com&lt;/a&gt;.
With their unmanaged service I get 1GB of RAM, 30GB of hard drive space,
and over 9TB of bandwidth, and I get it at a great price! So far the
service has been very stable, with only a few issues with the newest
Ubuntu VM images.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note that setting up your own Linux VPS is not for the faint of heart,
and should only be attempted by the more nerdy. :) Anyway, I got Apache
2 and PHP 5 setup, along with MySQL 5, Tomcat 6, and Railo running my
Coldfusion applications. I must say that it is &lt;em&gt;FAST&lt;/em&gt;, and I am most
pleased with that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did run into initial setup issue when I tried using the Ubuntu 9.10
image. MySQL would install, but put no default &lt;em&gt;root&lt;/em&gt; user for me to
administer with. The fix ended up being me going back to Ubuntu 8.04,
and those problems seemed to disappear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall this has been a good experience, and I hope it continues to be
so! Cheers!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CFFringe - The Open Source and Fringe CFML Conference</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/cffringe-the-open-source-and-fringe-cfml-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 02:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/cffringe-the-open-source-and-fringe-cfml-conference/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;According the the website &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cffringe.org&#34;&gt;www.cffringe.org&lt;/a&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CFFringe is the only CFML conference focused exclusively on open
source and fringe topics in CFML.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in getting into the open source CFML engines,
enhancing CFML engines through plugins or outright hacking, and
socializing with people doing cutting-edge things with CFML, this is the
place for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I encourage everyone to go to their website and register to stay tuned
to what I think is a great idea for a conference!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Certain Sports Company Gets a Bad Review</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/a-certain-sports-company-gets-a-bad-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/a-certain-sports-company-gets-a-bad-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As most of you know I tend to follow the various businesses in the
Dallas/Ft. Worth metroplex that use ColdFusion as their development
platform. I came across this article the other day about one such
business in the area that is not faring well with customer opinion.
Hopefully this business can turn things around for the better and
continue to contribute to area business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.fwbbbmember.com/PressRelease/eSportsPartners/tabid/296/Default.aspx&#34;&gt;http://www.fwbbbmember.com/PressRelease/eSportsPartners/tabid/296/Default.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice, Ice, Baby</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/ice-ice-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/ice-ice-baby/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday the family and I went out to Grapevine to see the Gaylord
Texan ICE! exhibit. With over 2 million pounds of ice in a 14,000 square
foot compound ICE was a very cool (literally and figuratively)
experience. Large parkas were provided to ward off the 9 degree
temperatures at this winter wonderland, but despite the chilly
atmosphere and fairly steep price, it was well worth the trouble and the
money. A very beautiful exhibit, and a fun time had by all.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaiian Falls</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/hawaiian-falls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2009 13:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/hawaiian-falls/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Maryanne, Taylor, and Aaliyah,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just wanted to write and say that I had a really great time at
Hawaiian Falls today. We swam in the pool, got wet by the giant bucket
of water, and went down several big slides with fast water tubes. I know
we ran out of sun screen a little too early, and Aaliyah, you got sick
for some reason after lunch, but you felt better afterwards, so it
turned out ok.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope that we get to go again to Hawaiian falls again soon together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love,
Daddy&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Linux and Windows Screen Sharing Software</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/free-linux-and-windows-screen-sharing-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 18:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/free-linux-and-windows-screen-sharing-software/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a sucker for cool applications. I also am a super-sucker for
&lt;strong&gt;FREE&lt;/strong&gt; cool applications. I was working on some code with my friend
Collin tonight and we had a need to take a look at some code together,
but we aren&amp;rsquo;t anywhere near each other. To further complicate matters
I&amp;rsquo;m running on Ubuntu Linux and he on Windows. After a quick search I
came across &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.yuuguu.com/home&#34;&gt;Yuuguu Instant Screen Sharing&lt;/a&gt;. What a neat program!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A simple download of a Debian package, and moments later I get a sign-up
screen. That too was painless, and before I knew it, I simply entered my
MSN account information, I selected Collin from the list, and clicked
Share. Kaboom!!! Awesomeness exploded onto my screen, and we were
sharing desktops before I knew it! Go give it a go!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weddings, Java, and a Good Weekend</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/weddings-java-and-a-good-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/weddings-java-and-a-good-weekend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quite an eventful weekend for Maryanne and I. Friday night we went out
to Sonny Bryan&amp;rsquo;s in downtown Dallas for Billy&amp;rsquo;s rehearsal dinner, and at
the same time to surprise Maryanne&amp;rsquo;s good friends Dana and John. We had
a smashing good time and stuffed ourselves completely with good BBQ. We
went home that night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday we packed up for the wedding at the Pegasus Room and our
subsequent stay at Hotel Magnolia. It was a nice room and hotel. The
Pegasus Room is apparently the old Dallas Power and Light building, and
had some really cool old architecture. I suppose the wedding was
beautiful, and I only suppose because we couldn&amp;rsquo;t see a thing. The room
was far too small, and we were seated on the side of the room. Basically
I could see the bride&amp;rsquo;s head. That&amp;rsquo;s it. :(&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the wedding there was a short hour for drinks back at the hotel,
then it was back to the Pegasus Room for the reception. It was a proper
party with a DJ, buffet, open bar, and the whole nine yards. A good
number of Jim Bean and cokes later it was time to head back to our
room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next morning we greeted the other guests for breakfast in a private
room with the newlyweds all a-glow. We then spent a good amount of time
carting Dana, John and family around, helping pack, unpack, and so on.
After lunch we all lounged around the pool for a while, then time for
home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile took some time to attempt to recreate some code Ben Nadel had
posted in ColdFusion for searching structures using a regular
expression, but in Java instead of CF. This was a fun exercise, except
that my blog&amp;rsquo;s code formatted looked crappy, so I spent several hours
getting a new formatter, and adjusting EVERY code blog entry. What a
pain. But in the end well worth it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>