<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Culture on Adam.Blog()</title>
    <link>http://adampresley.com/tags/culture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Culture on Adam.Blog()</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 15:21:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://adampresley.com/tags/culture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice, Ice, Baby</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/ice-ice-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/ice-ice-baby/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday the family and I went out to Grapevine to see the Gaylord
Texan ICE! exhibit. With over 2 million pounds of ice in a 14,000 square
foot compound ICE was a very cool (literally and figuratively)
experience. Large parkas were provided to ward off the 9 degree
temperatures at this winter wonderland, but despite the chilly
atmosphere and fairly steep price, it was well worth the trouble and the
money. A very beautiful exhibit, and a fun time had by all.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaiian Falls</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/hawaiian-falls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2009 13:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/hawaiian-falls/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Maryanne, Taylor, and Aaliyah,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just wanted to write and say that I had a really great time at
Hawaiian Falls today. We swam in the pool, got wet by the giant bucket
of water, and went down several big slides with fast water tubes. I know
we ran out of sun screen a little too early, and Aaliyah, you got sick
for some reason after lunch, but you felt better afterwards, so it
turned out ok.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope that we get to go again to Hawaiian falls again soon together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love,
Daddy&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Beer Commercial Ever</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/best-beer-commercial-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2008 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/best-beer-commercial-ever/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RyRvpR4XhK4&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to see one of
the funniest beer commercials ever.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preview of New Metallica Song!</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/preview-of-new-metallica-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/preview-of-new-metallica-song/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For those that know me, you probably know I&amp;rsquo;m a big Metal fan, and with
that comes being a Metallica fan (at least in my book it does). Here is
a video from the recent Ozzfest of their new song, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uRxNCJ0zhwk&amp;amp;feature=related&#34;&gt;Cyanide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movie Night - Beetlejuice</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/movie-night-beetlejuice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2007 12:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/movie-night-beetlejuice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last night was movie night. Again Maryanne and I hosted a movie night
starring the classic wacky movie, Beetlejuice. I forgot how fun that
movie is. What a blast! Katie and Tim from work made it, as well as
friends and neighbors Jeff and Andrea. We played quite a bit of Singstar
karaoke while eating a bit of greasy KFC chicken and biscuits. Mmmm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the movie Andrea and Jeff stuck around for some Guitar Hero and
more karaoke. Pictures? Only a few, as we kinda just forgot to take
more, sadly. But hey, karaoke, alcohol, and Beetlejuice? Good times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notice:&lt;/strong&gt; Pictures are no longer present.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monty Python Event</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/monty-python-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2007 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/monty-python-event/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This last Saturday night Maryanne and I hosted a movie watching party.
We invited several people but ended up with most not able to show, or
unable to at the last minute due to shifts in priority and schedule.
Just the same it turned out well though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had all the movie watching junk foods: M&amp;amp;Ms, chips, dips, candies,
cookies, &lt;strong&gt;POPCORN&lt;/strong&gt;, and pizza. We also had halves of coconuts to bang
together during the movie, as well as tiny &amp;ldquo;Holy Hand Grenades&amp;rdquo; to toss
at the screen at the bunny scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you didn&amp;rsquo;t make it, you shoulda!!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the Lot</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/on-the-lot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2007 02:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/on-the-lot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Perhaps a few of you have heard of that new reality show called &lt;em&gt;On the
Lot&lt;/em&gt;? Well, even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t, I suggest checking it out. If you are a
movie goer such as myself you might enjoy this. The premise is simple.
Take unknown, unheard of aspiring directors, give them challenges and
have them compete to win a $1 million dollar contract with DreamWorks
&amp;trade;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yup, that&amp;rsquo;s right. And the challenges are pretty cool. So far they have
had challenges where they have to work together, work against each
other, or make short movies that convey some type of thought, or in a
particular genre. So far, this show has promise. Let us see where it
goes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Pirates of the Caribbean: At World&#39;&#39;s End&#39;</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/pirates-of-the-caribbean-at-worlds-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2007 05:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/pirates-of-the-caribbean-at-worlds-end/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WARNING: Some Spoilers in here. Do not read if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to hear
about the movie before seeing.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, disclaimer out of the way, let&amp;rsquo;s talk pirates. The family,
girlfriend, and I went to see the latest in the Pirates of the Caribbean
franchise. Initial response? I like it. I&amp;rsquo;d give it a B+ overall. Yes, I
feel some of the magic is diminished, but this movie still has some
charm. All the old favorite characters are present to put their own
particular flavor into the movie mix, much like the last two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This movie continues from the second one where the East India Trading
Company is slated to take over the seas, and thus the world through the
possession of Davey Jones&amp;rsquo;s heart, and therefore the power he possess.
And it would seem they are well on their way. Apparently there is a
group of pirates that make up the Pirate Lords, and meet only on the
gravest of occasions to settle matters that are of importance to them.
This is one of those occasions. The idea? Release Calipso, the sea
goddess, from her human prison (yes, you met her in Pirates II) and back
into production, in hopes that she will aide the pirates against the
crusading Lord Beckett.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The biggest plot hole that I can see is this. How is Barbosa a pirate
lord at the same time that Jack is a pirate lord? In the first movie,
Barbosa was Jack&amp;rsquo;s first mate, and then Barbosa mutinied against Jack,
leaving Jack NOT a captain for about 8 years. If Jack was already a
pirate lord because he was the captain of the Black Pearl, how then did
Barbosa become one? Somewhere in between? If so, why did Jack keep his?
Yes, it feels a bit loose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anywho, a good flick, fun, and of course, make sure to stick around
AFTER the credits.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Robinsons</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/meet-the-robinsons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 09:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/meet-the-robinsons/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I took my baby girls to the movie &lt;em&gt;Meet the Robinsons&lt;/em&gt;. They enjoyed it,
even though my seven year old appears to be scared of all things 3D,
which is the version we went to see. There are two versions. The regular
3D animated version, and the TrueD 3D jump-at-ya version. Allow me to
state that the TrueD version was quite impressive. Very nice 3D effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall the movie was quite predictable, from start to finish. I will
say that it was enjoyable, however, and quite cute, peppered with a few
funny moments to keep the kids interested. I give it a B-. :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eragon</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/eragon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2006 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/eragon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Went to the movies for the first time in a while. Tabitha and I went and
saw Eragon. First allow me to state that I&amp;rsquo;ve never read the book(s), so
I had no particular expectations going into this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall the movie was pretty good. Nothing to write home about, but
really nice special effects, and when the action finally really kicked
in, good action sequences. I like some of the fantasy concepts put into
place here, so I suspect that the books are probably pretty good. I
think I shall get them.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A CD</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/a-cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2006 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/a-cd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, not too much to talk about. I bought a new CD today. Got turned on
to a band called Lacuna Coil. If you like the Goth Metal you&amp;rsquo;ll like
this. They also do a pretty bitchin cover of Depeche Mode&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Enjoy The
Silence&lt;/em&gt;. For those that like this kind of music, pick a CD up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://s3.amazonaws.com/www.adampresley.com/posts/karmacode_cdcover.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Karmacode CD Cover&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In other news...</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/in-other-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2006 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/in-other-news/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am loving the hell outta Guitar Hero 2. I got to play Laid to Rest -
Lamb of God, Beast and the Harlot - Avenged Sevenfold, and Hanger 18 -
Megadeth!! DUDE! So awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the cool new features include the encore when you do well on the
next to last song, and lots of strobe lights! Also, the band will jump
and hit the last note in unison at times. Very cool!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only thing wrong is that my second guitar is broke! NOOOO!! That
does, however, give me excuse to buy the &lt;strong&gt;wireless&lt;/strong&gt; Gibson Flying V!!!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Much Ado About Nothing</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/much-ado-about-nothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2006 17:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/much-ado-about-nothing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This year Shakespeare Festival of Dallas held their annual show at the
usual location in Samual Grand Park, but also at Addison Circle Park. So
I attended the Addison show. What started out to be a cool, brisk
evening turned out to be a blustery, windy event that chilled the
bones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aside from the weather the show was actually pretty good. I must say I
enjoyed it. The only items that I feel were a little off where the speed
of some delivery of the lines and couplets. A lot of it felt WAY too
rushed. I will note, however, that the set this year was very nice!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, good work!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>