<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Movies on Adam.Blog()</title>
    <link>http://adampresley.com/tags/movies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Movies on Adam.Blog()</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 12:12:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://adampresley.com/tags/movies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Horton Hits a Home Run</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/horton-hits-a-home-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 12:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/horton-hits-a-home-run/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a loveable classic of my childhood, I approached the movie &amp;ldquo;Horton
Hears A Who&amp;rdquo; with caution. It is not uncommon for Hollywood to screw up
movie renditions of things that I cherish. Ok, so maybe cherish is a
strong, girlie word&amp;hellip; How about awesome and cool. A stretch, but I
digress&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AnyWHO&amp;hellip; To be brief I have to say I walked away from this movie
feeling good, having a nice refreshing laugh. The animation is quite
good, with the Who&amp;rsquo;s being animated true to the original representations
found in the books crafted by the good Dr. himself. Jim Carey is good,
though a little over the top, but overall portrays a decent Horton.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very enjoyable.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movie Night - Beetlejuice</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/movie-night-beetlejuice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2007 12:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/movie-night-beetlejuice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last night was movie night. Again Maryanne and I hosted a movie night
starring the classic wacky movie, Beetlejuice. I forgot how fun that
movie is. What a blast! Katie and Tim from work made it, as well as
friends and neighbors Jeff and Andrea. We played quite a bit of Singstar
karaoke while eating a bit of greasy KFC chicken and biscuits. Mmmm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the movie Andrea and Jeff stuck around for some Guitar Hero and
more karaoke. Pictures? Only a few, as we kinda just forgot to take
more, sadly. But hey, karaoke, alcohol, and Beetlejuice? Good times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notice:&lt;/strong&gt; Pictures are no longer present.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Game Plan has Game</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/the-game-plan-has-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2007 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/the-game-plan-has-game/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Took the kiddos to see &amp;ldquo;The Rock&amp;rdquo; in his new movie, &lt;em&gt;The Game Plan&lt;/em&gt;. It
was fun! All the expected turns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Surprise, you&amp;rsquo;ve got a kid. Shake up your life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oh man, hard to get used to a kid. I&amp;rsquo;m rich, famous, and a football
player.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonding begins to occur. Starting to like your kid&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oops, I shouted something mean to you. You get hurt, and OMG I&amp;rsquo;m an
asshole.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Realization that your kid is important in your life sets in. Now you
don&amp;rsquo;t have her. Dummy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You start to suck at your job. She shows up, and you stop sucking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tears ensue, everyone wins, and is happy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The end.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will say that I did have a good time. Plenty of funny little quips,
and the magic between The Rock and Madison Pettis is really good. It
gets my family movie &amp;ldquo;A&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monty Python Event</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/monty-python-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2007 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/monty-python-event/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This last Saturday night Maryanne and I hosted a movie watching party.
We invited several people but ended up with most not able to show, or
unable to at the last minute due to shifts in priority and schedule.
Just the same it turned out well though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had all the movie watching junk foods: M&amp;amp;Ms, chips, dips, candies,
cookies, &lt;strong&gt;POPCORN&lt;/strong&gt;, and pizza. We also had halves of coconuts to bang
together during the movie, as well as tiny &amp;ldquo;Holy Hand Grenades&amp;rdquo; to toss
at the screen at the bunny scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you didn&amp;rsquo;t make it, you shoulda!!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surf&#39;s Up Wipes Out</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/surfs-up-wipes-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2007 03:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/surfs-up-wipes-out/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s right folks. Your&amp;rsquo;s truly took the girlfriend and kiddos to see
the movie Surf&amp;rsquo;s Up. Although touted as a funny movie, a great ride, I
found that Surf&amp;rsquo;s Up wiped out. The film concept was creative in that
they filmed it similar to a documentary. Instead of being entertained I
found myself getting up halfway through the movie to buy a slurpie. Yes,
I was that bored. Ok, so it had a couple of funny moments, but not
enough to warrant a good score.
Overall, I give it a C-.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Pirates of the Caribbean: At World&#39;&#39;s End&#39;</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/pirates-of-the-caribbean-at-worlds-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2007 05:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/pirates-of-the-caribbean-at-worlds-end/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WARNING: Some Spoilers in here. Do not read if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to hear
about the movie before seeing.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, disclaimer out of the way, let&amp;rsquo;s talk pirates. The family,
girlfriend, and I went to see the latest in the Pirates of the Caribbean
franchise. Initial response? I like it. I&amp;rsquo;d give it a B+ overall. Yes, I
feel some of the magic is diminished, but this movie still has some
charm. All the old favorite characters are present to put their own
particular flavor into the movie mix, much like the last two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This movie continues from the second one where the East India Trading
Company is slated to take over the seas, and thus the world through the
possession of Davey Jones&amp;rsquo;s heart, and therefore the power he possess.
And it would seem they are well on their way. Apparently there is a
group of pirates that make up the Pirate Lords, and meet only on the
gravest of occasions to settle matters that are of importance to them.
This is one of those occasions. The idea? Release Calipso, the sea
goddess, from her human prison (yes, you met her in Pirates II) and back
into production, in hopes that she will aide the pirates against the
crusading Lord Beckett.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The biggest plot hole that I can see is this. How is Barbosa a pirate
lord at the same time that Jack is a pirate lord? In the first movie,
Barbosa was Jack&amp;rsquo;s first mate, and then Barbosa mutinied against Jack,
leaving Jack NOT a captain for about 8 years. If Jack was already a
pirate lord because he was the captain of the Black Pearl, how then did
Barbosa become one? Somewhere in between? If so, why did Jack keep his?
Yes, it feels a bit loose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anywho, a good flick, fun, and of course, make sure to stick around
AFTER the credits.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Robinsons</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/meet-the-robinsons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 09:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/meet-the-robinsons/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I took my baby girls to the movie &lt;em&gt;Meet the Robinsons&lt;/em&gt;. They enjoyed it,
even though my seven year old appears to be scared of all things 3D,
which is the version we went to see. There are two versions. The regular
3D animated version, and the TrueD 3D jump-at-ya version. Allow me to
state that the TrueD version was quite impressive. Very nice 3D effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall the movie was quite predictable, from start to finish. I will
say that it was enjoyable, however, and quite cute, peppered with a few
funny moments to keep the kids interested. I give it a B-. :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eragon</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/eragon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2006 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/eragon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Went to the movies for the first time in a while. Tabitha and I went and
saw Eragon. First allow me to state that I&amp;rsquo;ve never read the book(s), so
I had no particular expectations going into this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall the movie was pretty good. Nothing to write home about, but
really nice special effects, and when the action finally really kicked
in, good action sequences. I like some of the fantasy concepts put into
place here, so I suspect that the books are probably pretty good. I
think I shall get them.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>