<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Games on Adam.Blog()</title>
    <link>http://adampresley.com/tags/games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Games on Adam.Blog()</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 19:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://adampresley.com/tags/games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Brawlin!</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/brawlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 19:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/brawlin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YES!&lt;/strong&gt; After a little more effort, and a bit more patience, we
&lt;strong&gt;FINALLY&lt;/strong&gt;got our multiplayer brawl to start up for Super Smash
Brothers Brawl. Bout f&amp;rsquo;n time! I switched out between Yoshi and Marth,
Josh switched out between Link and Ike, and Tabitha played Zelda, Donky
Kong, and Kirby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I then saved three of our matches to my SD card. After we finished
playing I reviewed each match for screenshots. To do this, the game
allows you to pause your reply at any point, zoom, pan, and rotate for
the best angles, and save screen shots. The &lt;strong&gt;BAD&lt;/strong&gt; thing about it is
that Nintendo, in their infinite wisdom, made it so that you can only
send them to another Brawl owner, or to an SD card. But even with the SD
card option they are BIN files, apparently raw image format. So I went a
hunting for a tool, and did find one called &lt;em&gt;bin2jpg&lt;/em&gt; that will convert
the BIN files to JPG files suitable for posting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brawl is fun... if you can connect</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/brawl-is-fun-if-you-can-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 19:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/brawl-is-fun-if-you-can-connect/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So my brother, his friend, and I tried to all hook up and have a nice
Super Smash Brothers Brawl beat-em up session on our Wii&amp;rsquo;s tonight.
Didn&amp;rsquo;t happen. Instead we spent over an hour trying to connect to each
other&amp;rsquo;s hosted games, letting each churn for over 10 minutes each, every
time either timing out, or just never connecting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It would seem that Nintendo was ill prepared for this kind of response.
I find this amusing due to the fact that this game was highly
anticipated for &lt;strong&gt;MONTHS&lt;/strong&gt; now, and you would think that with a game
this popular Nintendo would have beefed up the backend servers, ready to
take on the masses of rabit brawlers ready to do battle! Instead they
played conservative for their first &lt;em&gt;serious&lt;/em&gt; online venture, and I must
say that they are starting to disappoint. No connection tonight, laggy
connection last night&amp;hellip; All in all it is not looking like a good PR
campaign for the top selling video game giant right now.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reasons for Excitement</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/reasons-for-excitement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2007 05:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/reasons-for-excitement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two reasons for my excitement this morning, and I shall sum them up
promptly: Lord of the Rings Online content update, and Street Fighter
IV. That&amp;rsquo;s right, you heard it. Street Fighter IV! I LOVED the old
Street Fighter games. I grew up playing those in the arcades all day
long, and then on my Super Nintendo. Pimp times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And to make it even better this month Turbine will be releasing their
next major content update, Bood 11, for Lord of the Rings Online. This
update features grand coolness like player and kinship housing, complete
with furnishings and vendor discounts, and even taxidermy. Also on the
docket are new quests, and a brand new 12 player raid instance in which
you face off with a Balroq! Rock on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out both of these at these links:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gamesradar.com/us/ps3/game/news/article.&#34;&gt;Street Fighter IV&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lotro.turbine.com/article/421&#34;&gt;Book 11 - Lord of the Rings Online&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>