<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Family on Adam.Blog()</title>
    <link>http://adampresley.com/tags/family/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Family on Adam.Blog()</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2009 16:27:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://adampresley.com/tags/family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Ft. Worth Zoo 2009</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/ft-worth-zoo-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2009 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/ft-worth-zoo-2009/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A fun day in the sun at the Ft. Worth Zoo.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weddings, Java, and a Good Weekend</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/weddings-java-and-a-good-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/weddings-java-and-a-good-weekend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quite an eventful weekend for Maryanne and I. Friday night we went out
to Sonny Bryan&amp;rsquo;s in downtown Dallas for Billy&amp;rsquo;s rehearsal dinner, and at
the same time to surprise Maryanne&amp;rsquo;s good friends Dana and John. We had
a smashing good time and stuffed ourselves completely with good BBQ. We
went home that night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday we packed up for the wedding at the Pegasus Room and our
subsequent stay at Hotel Magnolia. It was a nice room and hotel. The
Pegasus Room is apparently the old Dallas Power and Light building, and
had some really cool old architecture. I suppose the wedding was
beautiful, and I only suppose because we couldn&amp;rsquo;t see a thing. The room
was far too small, and we were seated on the side of the room. Basically
I could see the bride&amp;rsquo;s head. That&amp;rsquo;s it. :(&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the wedding there was a short hour for drinks back at the hotel,
then it was back to the Pegasus Room for the reception. It was a proper
party with a DJ, buffet, open bar, and the whole nine yards. A good
number of Jim Bean and cokes later it was time to head back to our
room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next morning we greeted the other guests for breakfast in a private
room with the newlyweds all a-glow. We then spent a good amount of time
carting Dana, John and family around, helping pack, unpack, and so on.
After lunch we all lounged around the pool for a while, then time for
home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile took some time to attempt to recreate some code Ben Nadel had
posted in ColdFusion for searching structures using a regular
expression, but in Java instead of CF. This was a fun exercise, except
that my blog&amp;rsquo;s code formatted looked crappy, so I spent several hours
getting a new formatter, and adjusting EVERY code blog entry. What a
pain. But in the end well worth it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ceramic Pig Painting Fun!</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/ceramic-pig-painting-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2008 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/ceramic-pig-painting-fun/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just wanted to post up a couple of pictures of what Maryanne and the
girls worked on today. We had gone to &lt;a href=&#34;http://hobbylobby.com/&#34;&gt;Hobby Lobby&lt;/a&gt; to find some
craft-ie kind of stuff for the kids to do, and came across a neat
ceramic paint set. It contains three ceramic pigs, going from small to
large, and five or six paint colors. It&amp;rsquo;s neat because it just gives you
the pigs, paint, brushes, and lets you be as creative as you wish to
be!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dallas World Aquarium</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/dallas-world-aquarium/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2008 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/dallas-world-aquarium/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today Maryanne, the kids and I joined the whole family gang at the
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dwazoo.com/default.html&#34;&gt;Dallas World Aquarium&lt;/a&gt; for some fishy fun. Although fairly cool
outside the sun was shining and it turned out to be a nice day for an
outing. The Dallas Aquarium is a decent enough exhibit, featuring plenty
of fish, as well as bugs, birds, alligators, and more.The kids enjoyed
themselves at the many wonderous sights to behold. My biggest complaint
about this aquarium is the fact that it is far too confusing.With too
many twists and turns it is hard to remember where you have been, let
alone know where to go next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that we headed over to &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.babeschicken.com/&#34;&gt;Bebe&amp;rsquo;s Chicken&lt;/a&gt;, one of my favourite
places to eat. Some of the tastiest chicken around!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>