<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Presentation on Adam.Blog()</title>
    <link>http://adampresley.com/tags/presentation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Presentation on Adam.Blog()</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://adampresley.com/tags/presentation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>CCISD Career Day 2014</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/ccisd-career-day-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/ccisd-career-day-2014/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last night the I participated as a representative for computer programming at the Clear Creek ISD College and Career Fair night. The Clear Creek school district offers a number of programs that encourage students to jump start their future education and careers. The job fair is a way for students to talk to actual practitioners in their field of interest, or even learn about opportunities they may have never known about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last night was quite a success in my book. There were almost 100 tables representing business &amp;amp; marketing, agriculture, science and technology, education, transportation, and health services. Many tables had flashy backdrops, table covers, literature and demonstrations. I didn&amp;rsquo;t quite have the flash, but I did have a small presentation running on a loop on my giant gaming laptop, which can be found &lt;a href=&#34;http://careerday2014.adampresley.com/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was originally concerned I would not have many visitors. Programming isn&amp;rsquo;t considered to be &lt;em&gt;exciting&lt;/em&gt; by a lot of people I know. That concern was unfounded. I had a busy night! Lots of kids came by asking a wide array of questions, from &amp;ldquo;how much money will I make&amp;rdquo; to the student who is already teaching themselves or in Computer Science Pre-AP classes. I was very impressed with some students and their drive to learn on their own, asking great questions for advice on ways to learn even more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had a great time, and look forward to doing another if the opportunity arises. And maybe next time I&amp;rsquo;ll make some flashy booth backdrops!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://adampresley.com/assets/adampresley/images/posts/adam-career-day-2014.png&#34; alt=&#34;Adam at Career Day&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code for my Dallas TechFest 2010 Presentation Available</title>
      <link>http://adampresley.com/post/code-for-my-dallas-techfest-2010-presentation-available/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 04:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adampresley.com/post/code-for-my-dallas-techfest-2010-presentation-available/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Finally, as requested, my code and slides for my Dallas TechFest 2010
presentation are available for download. If you missed it I presented on
taking an existing ColdFusion application (could be anything, PHP, JSP,
Groovy + Grails) and incrementally spicing it up with &lt;a href=&#34;http://jquery.com&#34;&gt;jQuery&lt;/a&gt;. Click
&lt;a href=&#34;http://dl.dropbox.com/u/5726689/blog-downloads/MovieMania.zip&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to download the code!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>